<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- UI specific text -->
    <string name="app_name">Wetlands Watcher</string>
    <string name="noconnectionID">No Internet Connection!</string>
    <string name="satellite_menu_option">Enable Satellite Mode</string>
    <string name="about_menu_option">About this App</string>
    <string name="showMarkers">Show Points of Interest</string>
    <string name="listMarkers">List Markers</string>
    <string name="showTrails">Display the trails</string>
    <string name="showTrailsAlt">Display the KML trail layer</string>
    <string name="hideData">Hide data</string>
    <string name="satelliteOn">Satellite view on</string>
    <string name="satelliteOff">Satellite view off</string>
    <string name="snackBarToggle">Toggle</string>
    <string name="navShowTrails">View trail data</string>
    <string name="needTrailData">Get the trail data first!</string>
    <string name="detail_header1">Characteristics</string>
    <string name="detail_header2">Where to find it</string>
    <string name="list_toast">Touch an info marker for detailed information</string>

    <!-- Detail activity headers -->
    <string name="detail_about">About</string>
    <string name="detail_more">More</string>
    <string name="cattail">Cattails</string>
    <string name="tarplant">Tarplants</string>
    <string name="fitz">Fitz WERC</string>
    <string name="nature_center">Watsonville Nature Center</string>
    <string name="placeholder">Placeholder</string>

    <!-- Detail activity information -->
    <string name="fitz_about">The Fitz Wetlands Educational Resource Center (Fitz WERC) promotes research on, education about,
        and conservation of the wetlands and watersheds of the Pajaro Valley.
        The Fitz WERC is a joint project of the City of Watsonville, the Pajaro Valley Unified School District,
        and the Watsonville Wetlands Watch.</string>
    <string name="fitz_more"><![CDATA[
    <a href="http://www.fitzwerc.org/">More information may be found at their website.</a>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="nature_center_about">The Watsonville Nature Center is a great place to bring the whole family!
        Beautiful interactive and educational exhibits are appropriate for all ages.
        The Kid’s Corner is filled with bilingual books, arts and crafts, and nature activities.
        Sunday afternoons feature free outdoor bilingual guided nature walks on our award winning trails.</string>
    <string name="nature_center_more"><![CDATA[
    <a href="http://cityofwatsonville.org/public-works-utilities/conservation_outreach_and_education_program/nature-center">More information may be found at their website.</a>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="cattail_characteristics">This plant is one of the most common plants growing in freshwater wetlands.
        It has long, flat light-green leaves and creeping roots. The flowers are at the end of a long
        stalk that looks like a hot dog on a stick. The fuzzy down that hangs on the cattails carries
        the seeds in the wind.
    </string>
    <string name="cattail_where">Cattails grow in fresh water in every finger of the Watsonville Slough system.</string>
    <string name="cattail_life_cycle">It flowers from June to July</string>
    <string name="cattail_uses">The leaves were used for weaving mats for houses. Native Americans made toy cattail dolls. Please see our statement on the use of plants.</string>
    <string name="cattail_fact">Look closely when you walk by a colony of cattails. Cattails provide habitat and food for many nesting birds, muskrats and other animals.</string>

    <string name="tarplant_characteristics">The tarplant is an aromatic, glandular annual herb in the sunflower
        family (Asteraceae), growing 10-50 cm (4-20 inches) tall. Small plants may produce a single yellow
        daisy-like flower head on a single stem, while larger plants have a rigid main stem and lateral
        branches that grow to the height of the main stem and produce many flowers.
        It is coated with a sticky, resinous material that helps to retard water loss during the heat of
        the day and may also help to repel potential predators.
    </string>
    <string name="tarplant_where">It typically grows on deep loam and sandy loam soils with a subsurface clay component,
        which hold moisture longer into the growing season compared to the surrounding sandy soils.
        It is frequently associated with non-native grasses such as wild oat, barley, rattlesnake grass,
        vulpia, and bromes. Native associates include rushes, California oatgrass, and other tarplants.
        The species is often found where disturbances maintain a short vegetation canopy through the growing season.</string>
    <string name="tarplant_fact">Its beautiful flower heads color the otherwise dry fields of mid summer,
        attracting an interesting array of pollinators.</string>

    <string name="restoration_info">Wetlands are a valuable natural resource that have been widely degraded. The islands you see behind the Nature Center are restored for a variety of birds and other wildlife.
        Removal and exotic invasive weeds is the first step in returning these areas to natural health.
        Weeds are replaced with native California plants that promote biodiversity and provide habitat for native wildlife.</string>

    <string name="aboutText"> <!-- Use CDATA to prevent android from parsing html tags -->
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>About</h1><p>This mobile application is created during the HACK UCSC 2015 competition
        to create a mobile interface to display trails and points of interest in the Watsonville Wetlands as a project for the Watsonville Wetlands
        Watch. As an initial prototype but now a mobile map that can be opened from a browser, we also created an interactive map to display data. We used Google Maps API for both applications. </p>
        <p>Authors:<br />
        Android Application Developer: Edmond Lee<br />
        Web Application Developers: Matthew Smithey, Andre Nuygen Van Qui, Sergy Pretensky<br />
            Other Team Members: Rosa Ayala </p><br />
        <p>Watsonville Wetlands Watch members: Noelle Antolin, Darren </p>
        <p><a href="https://github.com/IamTechknow/trailapp">Trail App on Github</a><br />
            <a href="http://watsonvillewetlandswatch.org/">Watsonville Wetlands Watch Site</a></p>
        <p>About Watsonville Wetlands Watch: <br />
        <blockquote>
        &quot;Watsonville Wetlands Watch advocates for wetland issues, educates elementary, middle, and high school students,
        restores degraded habitats, preserves what remains whole, and teaches appreciation for the unique beauty and life
        of the Pajaro Valley wetlands. In cooperation with numerous other agencies, we support studies of and planning
        for these sites.&quot;</blockquote></p>
        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
